Ravens fans, I am so excited to sit down
with the newest member of the team, Trey
Hendrickson. Trey, you are a Baltimore
Raven. What does it mean when you hear
that?
>> It's an established defensive [music]
culture, and I'm excited to be a part of
that and see what this 2026 brand uh can
bring, and I'm excited to be a Raven.
>> Trey, you've played the scene many times
over the years being on the Bengals and
being in this division. But when you
[music] drive into the facility here and
you and you walk through and you realize
that you're part of this team now,
you're part of this organization and
this culture, what are the thoughts and
the emotions that come to mind? [music]
It
>> was incredibly welcoming, right? And you
can tell that they're very passionate
about their team and spare no expense,
make sure that we have [music] the best
of the best, very humbling to be a part
of this process and and the incredible
opportunity that this [music] team with
the talent and this new coaching staff
brings. and I plan on being a huge part
of that.
>> So Trey, when free agency opened,
everybody knew that you were going to be
one of the top guys out there. And
there's a lot of teams, I'm sure,
[music] calling you, calling your agent,
trying to get you to come to their
clubs. What was it about the
conversations with the Ravens that
ultimately made you [music] feel like
this is the place I want to go and
really invest in uh becoming a Baltimore
Raven?
>> Being a Raven is [music] winning games
and in defense, too. Like I said, um
wonderful opportunity [music] for me and
my family. It gives me a fresh start.
Um, it's a division that I know. It's an
incredible opportunity to rush the
passer. [music] It's just an tremendous
blessing and and God has been so good to
me in this process, but through the
adversity and through the ups and downs
and all the doors that have opened for
me and it's just um what a wonderful
opportunity. [music]
>> At what point did you start to envision
yourself in the purple and black? Uh,
you know, it's one of those things that
it when it came [music] to be and and
now I'm looking at, you know, these
graphics, I'm excited to get in the
uniform and I'm excited to start really
getting from the ground level up OTAAS
[music] training camp and building what
it means to be a part of an organization
like this.
>> Something that struck me during the
press conference that you had was you
talked about playing in the AFC North
and how it fits [music] you kind of a
nasty brand of football and that's
something that that you really embrace.
Tell me a little bit about that
mentality. [music]
>> Yeah, it's physical, right? like the
line of scrimmage matters and affecting
the quarterback matters. There's a lot
of talent in this division at [music]
the quarterback spot and uh you know,
one of these things that excites me is
this division is gritty. [music]
You know, it's it's hit with your hands
and drive on the block and and playing
with guys that have been in this league
for a long time [music] uh respect this
division if they have to play the
opponents on their schedule. So, it's
it's got a lot of respect leaguewide.
It's an incredible opportunity to wear
purple and black and um obviously to get
after the quarterback.
>> The word that head coach Jesse Mentor
used [music] in talking about you was
closer and this is something that this
team has been looking for fourth
quarter, [music] third downs, somebody
who can step up in those big moments on
defense. How do you relish the
expectations and the responsibility that
come with being a guy who can close out
games on the defensive [music] side of
the ball?
>> Yeah, I've never really looked at it
like that. I've looked at it as the hard
[music] work I put in from the
beginning. And that's all the way back
in high school and the fundamentals I've
learned through the process and [music]
where do you put your eyes, hands, and
feet. Those are the things that people
just think maybe a sack just happens.
It's tiring your opponent out. It's
being ready for the opportunity. [music]
It's closing when the time comes and the
team needs you. Are you the guy that
wants to step up and make that play or
are you the guy that says, "Ah, somebody
else is going to take care of it for
us." I personally am motivated to be a
guy that helps affect us in a positive
way, affect the game in a way we can get
the ball [music] back to Lamar Jackson
and and put it in his hands so that he
can take care of the game. Just being a
part of that process has been humbling
over the last nine years. Um, for guys
to rely on me, it's uh I I would like
people to count on me and but that comes
through [music] the discipline that I
hold myself to getting to that closing
moment. Trey, everything I've heard
about you and and and read and and and
talking to people, everyone talks about
your work ethic and how that's part of
uh what makes you go and that's part of
what's made you such a great player to
to get this contract here in year 10.
Where does that work ethic come from?
>> My father uh worked very hard for our
family. There was uh to to see him work,
I mean, he was Superman to me and uh you
know, he instilled that into all of our
our family. My brother is a mechanical
and aerospace engineer. He graduated
with his masters at Purdue. My sister's
the head of HR at Admin Health in
Orlando and um you know very wise,
disciplined, hardworking people and
successful and um for me it was always
sports and going going harder than other
people in sixth grade and down and backs
in basketball or whether it's running
through the line uh in everything you
do. It's the discipline that I was
talking about that carries you to these
moments and when you can close it's
because of the process that I've been
doing for the last 30 years.
>> That's awesome. You mentioned Lamar
Jackson and and the excitement of
playing alongside him and being part of
this team with him. Just how glad are
you that you don't have to chase him
around anymore?
>> Yeah. Well, you know, tremendous athlete
um MVP multiple times in the league.
Incredible. It's exciting to have me as
a defender get him the ball back cuz I
know how special he is and uh you know
that's the opportunity I'm looking
forward to is getting him the ball,
watching him do his thing [music] and
then when the time comes that we need to
end games, we will. something that you
the Ravens have been a team that's been
knocking on the door. They've been right
there and they're looking to get to that
next level. You've been to a Super Bowl.
Um what does it take to for a team to
come together and get to that point? And
you you talked about in your press
conference that at this stage of your
career, you want an opportunity to
compete for that Lombardi? What does it
take to help a team get to that point?
>> Well, it's built in OTAAS, right? like
it starts in OTAAS and it's established
in training camp and you have preeason
and then you get going in the regular
season and there's there's a limited
amount of opportunities. So, making the
most of those and coming together as a
nucleus under a new coaching uh scheme
is is something that's important from
the ground up so that I can be a part of
it as soon as possible is important to
me.
>> So, Trey, you've played at MT Bank
Stadium plenty of times. You've had
these moments uh in that stadium. You
know what it's like. you know what it's
like to take the field there on big
games and under the lights and the
excitement that comes of playing in that
stadium as you think about taking the
field in a Ravens uniform for the first
time and running out of that tunnel and
hearing the ovation from Baltimore fans.
What are the thoughts and the emotions
that come to your mind? Well, I'm
extremely excited and there's a lot of
history in defense I hinted to earlier
and uh the guys that have run through
that tunnel. Uh you pay tribute to them,
but the way you play and that's what
excites me about the AFC North and and
everything that comes with it. It's it's
gritty. It's tough and you know, I'm
excited to embrace the city and and the
way they've had their culture and and
being a part of that and learning the
system and and bringing my brand of
football to here is something I'm
excited about.
>> Well, look, I'm going to fire up about
it. I know Ravens fans are as well. So
congratulations and welcome to
Baltimore.
>> Thank you.